Finding Aid for the Albert McCleery Papers PASC.0098
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects, 1950-1960; (1-3, 5, 7, 8, 10-20, 22)
  - MANHATTAN
    - If I Should Die - final draft of episode (1 item), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - If I Should Die - final drafts (one copy with timmings) (2 items), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - If I Should Die - second draft script by Anthony Spinner (1 item), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - If I Should Die - set design (11 items), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - If I Should Die (11 items), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Sponsors' comments; cast, prop, and personnel lists; show rundown; credits; and taping and rehearsal schedules.
    - If I Should Die (originally titled In the Wee Small Hours) - casting ideas for, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - If I Should Die" (originally titled: "The Wee, Small Hours") (1 item), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      First draft by Anthony Spinner.
    - Image (The) - treatment and script by George Bellak (3 items), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Series' proposal (2 drafts) and one production schedule (3 items), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - NBC MATINEE THEATRE
    - Correspondence dealing with radio simulcast productions of the series (2 items), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Facts and figures concerning first six weeks of p roduction and progress report 1955 (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Interoffice correspondence (58 items), 1955 October- August 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Discussions on episode synopsis, working facilities, hiring suggestions, publicity, and scheduling.
    - Letters from the Lutheran Television associates and a letter of response to an angry viewer (4 items), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Letters to General Mills and Pillsbury regarding their possible interest in sponsoring the series (2 items), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - List of actors and plays requested by viewers in fan mail (2 items), no date (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - List of writers and stories under consideration 1955 (8 items) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Lists of addresses and phone numbers of personnel involved with the series (7 items), 1957, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Lists of character descriptions (2 items), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Represents six MATINEE plays, three of which match actors with their roles.
    - MATINEE publicity in the form of magazine and NBC sales department advertisements (20 items), 1955, 1956, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Press releases on various MATINEE actors (3 items), no date (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Radio and television continuity acceptance reports (7 items), 1955 November- May 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Sponsors' advertisement booklets 1956 (6 items) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Synopses of and comments on published material under consideration for television adaptation (Approximately 75 items), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 25 Words or Less, 12/23/1957 (Box 55)
    - 25th Hour (The), 5/7/1956 (Box 30)
    - Accent on Youth, 2/1/1957 (Box 41)
    - Adjustable Mr Willing (The), 9/9/1957 (Box 51)
    - Aftermath, 5/20/1957 (Box 46)
    - All the World Over, 11/12/1957 (Box 54)
    - Alleyway (The), 3/26/1958 (Box 60)
    - Allison's House, 6/15/1956 (Box 32)
    - Almost Any Man Will Do, 10/18/1957 (Box 53)
    - American (The), 6/5/1956 (Box 31)
    - Among Strangers, 9/6/1957 (Box 51)
    - And Then There Were Three, 10/24/1956 (Box 37)
    - Angel Face, 8/28/1957 (Box 51)
    - Angel Street, 5/9/1958 (Box 62)
    - Ann Veronica, 7/29/1957 (Box 50)
    - Ann Veronica (Commercials), 11/21/1957 (Box 54)
    - Another Sky, 7/25/1956 (Box 34)
    - Antidote (The), 3/21/1956 (Box 27)
    - Anxious Night, 3/18/1958 (Box 59)
    - Anxious Years (The), 2/9/1956 (Box 25)
    - Anything but Love, 2/29/1956 (Box 26)
    - Anything for a Laugh, 1/29/1957 (Box 41)
    - Are You Listening, 9/3/1956 (Box 35)
    - Arms and the Man, 1/16/1957 (Box 41)
    - Arms and the Man (Commercials), 4/23/1957 (Box 45)
    - Arrowsmith, 12/5/1955 (Box 23)
    - As Young as You Feel, 2/7/1956 (Box 25)
    - Ask Me No Questions, 4/20/1956 (Box 29)
    - Autumn Crocus, 6/8/1956 (Box 31)
    - Awakening (The), 8/27/1957 (Box 51)
    - Awakening (The) (Commercials), 1/30/1958 (Box 58)
    - Babylonian Heart, 4/19/1956 (Box 29)
    - Bachelor Father, 6/3/1957 (Box 47)
    - Backfire, 7/12/1956 (Box 33)
    - Baron and the Banshees (The), 3/16/1956 (Box 27)
    - Barricade on the Big Black (Comm), 8/26/1957 (Box 51)
    - Barricade on the Big Black (Comm), 3/27/1957 (Box 44)
    - Battle of the Paper Bullets (The) program budget and a tentative budget (2 items), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Belong to Me, 7/31/1956 (Box 34)
    - Best Friend in Town (The), 5/15/1957 (Box 46)
    - Beyond a Reasonable Doubt, 11/8/1955 (Box 22)
    - Big Box (The), 1/23/1956 (Box 25)
    - Big Guy (The), 3/14/1956 (Box 27)
    - Big Hearted Gerbert, 5/10/1957 (Box 46)
    - Big Hearted Herbert, 11/11/1955 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Present, 6/27/1956 (Box 33)
    - Bishop Misbehaves (The), 7/13/1956 (Box 33)
    - Black Chiffon, 7/6/1956 (Box 33)
    - Blind Date, 5/16/1956 (Box 30)
    - Blind Man's Bluff, 4/17/1957 (Box 45)
    - Bobbie, 2/20/1957 (Box 42)
    - Bottle Imp (The), 5/22/1956 (Box 31)
    - Boy Grows Up (A), 4/22/1958 (Box 61)
    - Boys Will Be Men, 7/30/1957 (Box 50)
    - Brass Ring (The), 12/1/1955 (Box 23)
    - Brat's House (The), 2/11/1957 (Box 42)
    - Brat's House (The) (Commercials), 7/19/1957 (Box 49)
    - Bread upon the Waters, 3/28/1956 (Box 28)
    - Break Upon the Waters (Comm), 3/12/1957 (Box 43)
    - Bridge (The), 2/22/1957 (Box 42)
    - Brief Candle, 6/28/1957 (Box 48)
    - Brief Music, 5/23/1956 (Box 31)
    - Bright Boy, 4/27/1956 (Box 29)
    - But Fear Itself, 6/26/1956 (Box 32)
    - But When She Was Bad, 7/11/1957 (Box 49)
    - But You Look Like Sisters, 4/5/1956 (Box 28)
    - Cadenza, 11/25/1957 (Box 54)
    - Call It a Day, 7/26/1957 (Box 50)
    - Candle in the Dark, 11/14/1956 (Box 38)
    - Canterville Ghost (The), 4/15/1958 (Box 61)
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, 12/14/1956 (Box 39)
    - Career Angel, 3/13/1958 (Box 59)
    - Carefree Tree (The), 4/30/1956 (Box 29)
    - Carefree Tree (The) (Commercials), 3/11/1957 (Box 43)
    - Case of Fear (A), 4/10/1958 (Box 60)
    - Case of Pure Fiction, 2/13/1957 (Box 42)
    - Cask of Amontillado (Commercials), 1/29/1958 (Box 57)
    - Cask of Amontillado (The), 7/16/1957 (Box 49)
    - Catbird Seat (The), 2/17/1956 (Box 26)
    - Cause for Suspicion, 6/6/1956 (Box 31)
    - Cave In (Commercials), 5/16/1958 (Box 62)
    - Cave In (Commercials), 2/3/1958 (Box 58)
    - Cease from Anger, 11/26/1956 (Box 39)
    - Chance to Die (A), 1/10/1958 (Box 57)
    - Charcoal Pink, 2/10/1958 (Box 58)
    - Charmer (The), 6/26/1957 (Box 48)
    - Child and the Muse (The), 1/20/1956 (Box 25)
    - Children of Papa Juan (The), 5/29/1956 (Box 31)
    - Church on Monday, 5/2/1957 (Box 46)
    - Clippings, 1955 Aug-May 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Reviews and commentary on NBC MATINEE, McCleery, and actors featured in the program. 75 itmes.
    - Cloud for Jeni (A), 12/6/1957 (Box 55)
    - Cold Christmas, 12/24/1956 (Box 40)
    - Collected Letters of Mr Sage (The), 1/7/1958 (Box 56)
    - Company Manners, 1/19/1956 (Box 24)
    - Consul (The), 12/9/1957 (Box 55)
    - Contingent Fee (The), 3/14/1958 (Box 59)
    - Cordially with Bombs, 12/8/1955 (Box 23)
    - Course for Collision, 6/13/1958 (Box 63)
    - Courtship of Miles Standish, 11/23/1955 (Box 22)
    - Cowboy for Chris (A), 3/12/1956 (Box 27)
    - Crime at Blossoms, 6/13/1956 (Box 32)
    - Cupid Rode a Horse, 8/7/1956 (Box 34)
    - Cypress Tree (The), 7/30/1956 (Box 34)
    - Daisy Mayme, 1/20/1958 (Box 57)
    - Damask Cheek (The), 6/22/1956 (Box 32)
    - Dandy Dick, 3/20/1958 (Box 59)
    - Daniel Webster and the Sea Serpent, 11/29/1957 (Box 54)
    - Dark of the Moon, 12/13/1957 (Box 55)
    - Dark Victory, 1/4/1957 (Box 40)
    - Daughter of Kings, 12/31/1957 (Box 56)
    - Daughter of Mata Hari (The), 4/3/1957 (Box 44)
    - Daughter of the 7th, 5/3/1956 (Box 29)
    - Daughters of the Seventh, 1/28/1957 (Box 41)
    - Day of Discoveries, 5/22/1958 (Box 62)
    - Death Takes a Holiday, 4/8/1958 (Box 60)
    - Decision, 1/24/1958 (Box 57)
    - Declaration (The), 7/4/1956 (Box 33)
    - Design for Glory, 4/1/1958 (Box 60)
    - Devil's Violin (The), 2/28/1958 (Box 59)
    - Diamond (The), 2/3/1956 (Box 25)
    - Dinner at Antione's, 3/5/1956 (Box 27)
    - Dispossessed (The), 11/24/1955 (Box 23)
    - Doctor's Wife (The), 4/18/1956 (Box 29)
    - Double Door, 1/5/1956 (Box 24)
    - Dr Jekyl & Mr Hyde (Commercials), 8/16/1957 (Box 51)
    - Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde, 3/8/1957 (Box 43)
    - Dracula, 11/23/1956 (Box 38)
    - Dram of Poison (A), 11/8/1956 (Box 38)
    - Dream That Was Fixed, 5/30/1957 (Box 47)
    - Eden End, 2/17/1958 (Box 58)
    - Edwina Black, 5/18/1956 (Box 30)
    - Egoist (The), 10/16/1956 (Box 37)
    - Elementals (Commercials), 5/5/1958 (Box 61)
    - Embassy House, 11/18/1957 (Box 54)
    - Embattled Maiden, 5/13/1957 (Box 46)
    - Emma, 9/16/1957 (Box 52)
    - Empty Nest (The), 11/27/1956 (Box 39)
    - End of a Season, 6/3/1958 (Box 63)
    - End of a Sentence, 5/2/1958 (Box 61)
    - End of the Rope, 4/1/1957 (Box 44)
    - Eugenie Grandet, 12/21/1956 (Box 40)
    - Eugenie Grandet (Commercials), 8/12/1957 (Box 50)
    - Europeans (The), 1/6/1958 (Box 56)
    - Everything Is Relative, 12/31/1956 (Box 40)
    - Explorer (The), 4/25/1956 (Box 29)
    - Eye of the Storm (Commercials), 6/7/1957 (Box 47)
    - Eye of the Storm (The) (Comm), 10/1/1957 (Box 52)
    - Fable of Harry (The), 7/12/1957 (Box 49)
    - Fall of the House of Usher (Comm), 11/5/1957 (Box 53)
    - Fall of the House of Usher (Comm), 4/28/1958 (Box 61)
    - Fall of the House of Usher (The), 8/6/1956 (Box 34)
    - Family Affair (A), 5/14/1956 (Box 30)
    - Family Man (The), 10/17/1956 (Box 37)
    - Father Comes Home!, 10/15/1957 (Box 53)
    - Fawn (The), 8/1/1957 (Box 50)
    - Feast (The), 7/19/1956 (Box 34)
    - Fiddlin' Man, 4/9/1956 (Box 28)
    - Fight the Whole World (Comm), 12/17/1957 (Box 56)
    - Fight the Whole World (Comm), 5/13/1958 (Box 62)
    - Finley's Fan Club, 8/6/1957 (Box 50)
    - First Captain (The), 7/22/1957 (Box 49)
    - First Love, 8/13/1957 (Box 50)
    - First Year (The), 3/29/1957 (Box 44)
    - Flashing Stream (The), 4/12/1957 (Box 45)
    - For Sweetheart, Wife, or Mother, 12/26/1956 (Box 40)
    - For These Services, 12/7/1955 (Box 23)
    - Forbidden Search (Commercials), 10/4/1957 (Box 52)
    - Forbidden Search (The), 7/31/1957 (Box 50)
    - Forever and Ever, 1/23/1958 (Box 57)
    - Forsaking All Others, 6/9/1956 (Box 32)
    - Found Money, 4/17/1958 (Box 61)
    - Frankenstein, 2/5/1957 (Box 42)
    - Freedom Comes Later, 9/10/1957 (Box 51)
    - From the Desk of Margaret Tydings, 2/18/1957 (Box 42)
    - From the Desk of Margaret Tydings, 4/14/1958 (Box 60)
    - Gallin--All American, 12/21/1955 (Box 24)
    - Gate (The), 1/9/1956 (Box 24)
    - Gentleman Caller, 12/19/1957 (Box 55)
    - Gentleman of Fortune (A), 12/18/1957 (Box 55)
    - George Has a Birthday, 11/1/1956 (Box 38)
    - George Has a Birthday, 6/9/1956 (Box 32)
    - Ghost of Greenwich Village (The), 6/28/1956 (Box 33)
    - Giant Killer, 3/29/1956 (Box 28)
    - Gift and the Giver (The), 12/16/1957 (Box 55)
    - Gioconda Smile (The), 5/3/1957 (Box 46)
    - Give Me a Wand, 12/11/1957 (Box 55)
    - Golden Door (The), 6/4/1957 (Box 47)
    - Golden Fleecing (The), 1/22/1958 (Box 57)
    - Good Housekeeping, 5/8/1958 (Box 62)
    - Goodbye on Thursday, 2/20/1958 (Box 58)
    - Gramercy Ghost, 9/7/1956 (Box 35)
    - Grandmama & the Grandfather Clock, 11/8/1957 (Box 54)
    - Graybeards and Witches, 5/1/1956 (Box 29)
    - Great Big Guy, 4/29/1958 (Box 61)
    - Great Obstacle Courtship, 1/9/1958 (Box 56)
    - Green Shores (The), 11/26/1957 (Box 54)
    - Growing Wonder (A), 5/31/1957 (Box 47)
    - Guardians of the Temple, 4/30/1957 (Box 46)
    - Guest at the Embassy (A), 5/21/1957 (Box 46)
    - Guest Cottage (The), 6/19/1956 (Box 32)
    - Guest of Questway (The), 5/7/1958 (Box 62)
    - Gwendolen Harleth's Story, 5/28/1957 (Box 47)
    - Hand-Me-Down, 9/13/1957 (Box 52)
    - Hands, 5/30/1958 (Box 62)
    - Happy Rest (The), 1/6/1956 (Box 24)
    - Hat, A Coat, A Glove (A), 4/26/1957 (Box 45)
    - Haven's End, 8/20/1957 (Box 51)
    - Heart of a Husband (The), 4/3/1956 (Box 28)
    - Heart of Mary Lincoln (The), 2/10/1956 (Box 25)
    - Hearthstones, 9/26/1957 (Box 52)
    - Heed the Falling Sparrow, 8/21/1957 (Box 51)
    - Hemlock Cup (The), 3/5/1957 (Box 43)
    - Here We Are, 1/15/1957 (Box 41)
    - Herself Alone, 5/30/1956 (Box 31)
    - Hex (The), 1/10/1957 (Box 40)
    - Hickory Heart (The), 2/27/1958 (Box 59)
    - Hickory Limb (The), 2/21/1957 (Box 42)
    - High Places (The), 7/5/1956 (Box 33)
    - Hold My Hand and Run, 2/1/1956 (Box 25)
    - Hollow Woman (The), 10/11/1956 (Box 36)
    - Home at Seven, 7/27/1956 (Box 34)
    - Home is the Hunter, 1/17/1957 (Box 41)
    - Home on the Range, 1/13/1958 (Box 57)
    - Horns of a Dilemma, 12/28/1955 (Box 24)
    - Horsepower (Commercials), 8/19/1957 (Box 51)
    - Horsepower (Commercials), 4/18/1957 (Box 45)
    - House Next Door (The), 9/25/1956 (Box 36)
    - House of Mirth (The), 12/4/1956 (Box 39)
    - House of the Seven Gables (The), 4/6/1956 (Box 28)
    - House Off Fifth Avenue (The), 8/28/1956 (Box 35)
    - House on Wildwood Lane (The), 11/7/1955 (Box 22)
    - House with Golden Streets (A), 1/3/1958 (Box 56)
    - Hymn to the Dedicated, 5/8/1957 (Box 46)
    - I Like It Here, 10/26/1956 (Box 37)
    - I Want to March, 2/24/1956 (Box 26)
    - Ice Man (The) (Commercials), 5/15/1958 (Box 62)
    - Ice Man (The) (Commercials), 2/4/1958 (Box 58)
    - Impersonal Touch (The), 9/20/1957 (Box 52)
    - Importance of Being Earnest (The), 2/8/1957 (Box 42)
    - In the Dread of Winter, 4/17/1956 (Box 29)
    - In the Fog, 9/11/1957 (Box 51)
    - Inspector General (The), 4/2/1958 (Box 60)
    - Invisible Man (The), 8/8/1957 (Box 50)
    - Invisible Man (The) (Commercials), 12/30/1957 (Box 56)
    - Iris, 11/14/1957 (Box 54)
    - It Came from Out of Town, 4/30/1958 (Box 61)
    - Ivy Curtain (The) (Commercials), 11/6/1957 (Box 53)
    - Ivy Curtain (The) (Commercials), 4/16/1958 (Box 61)
    - Jamie Picks a Wife, 4/16/1957 (Box 45)
    - Jane Eyre (Commercials), 10/8/1957 (Box 52)
    - Jason, 12/2/1955 (Box 23)
    - Jigsaw, 11/14/1955 (Box 22)
    - Johnny, 5/11/1956 (Box 30)
    - Johnson House (The), 11/20/1957 (Box 54)
    - Lady Chooses (The), 11/22/1955 (Box 22)
    - Lady's Maid's Bell (The), 9/4/1956 (Box 35)
    - Last Battlefield (The), 2/16/1956 (Box 26)
    - Last Hour (The), 7/18/1957 (Box 49)
    - Last Leaf (The) (Commercials), 11/22/1957 (Box 54)
    - Last Leaf (The) (Commercials), 3/22/1957 (Box 44)
    - Last Stop (The), 10/28/1957 (Box 53)
    - Last Voyage (The), 7/4/1957 (Box 49)
    - Last Voyage (The) (Commercials), 4/21/1958 (Box 61)
    - Late Date, 9/28/1956 (Box 36)
    - Laugh a Little Tear, 8/7/1957 (Box 50)
    - Laugh a Little Tear (Commercials), 2/19/1958 (Box 58)
    - Ledger (The), 2/22/1956 (Box 26)
    - Legend of Jenny Lind (The), 5/2/1956 (Box 29)
    - Lest We Forget, 10/23/1957 (Box 53)
    - Letter from Johnny Brack (A), 9/20/1956 (Box 36)
    - Letter of Introduction, 7/26/1956 (Box 34)
    - Life upon the Wicked Stage, 2/12/1958 (Box 58)
    - Light and Shadow, 1/27/1956 (Box 25)
    - Light in the Sky (A), 6/25/1957 (Box 48)
    - Little Minister, 12/26/1957 (Box 56)
    - Little Women, 12/25/1956 (Box 40)
    - Liza, 6/17/1957 (Box 48)
    - Location of Roycemore College (The), 11/21/1956 (Box 38)
    - Lonesome Husband, 5/24/1957 (Box 47)
    - Long, Long Laugh (The), 2/5/1958 (Box 58)
    - Long, Long Laugh (The), 5/14/1958 (Box 62)
    - Look out for John Tucker!, 6/4/1958 (Box 63)
    - Lost Survivors (The), 8/14/1957 (Box 50)
    - Lost Survivors (The) (Commercials), 4/7/1958 (Box 60)
    - Love is a Locksmith, 12/12/1956 (Box 39)
    - Love Out of Town, 1/31/1958 (Box 58)
    - Love out of Town (Commercials), 6/2/1958 (Box 62)
    - Love, Honor and O'Day, 6/21/1956 (Box 32)
    - Lovers (The), 9/10/1956 (Box 35)
    - Luck of Amos Currie (The), 6/14/1956 (Box 32)
    - M is for the Many-------, 3/23/1956 (Box 27)
    - Mad Money, 9/19/1956 (Box 36)
    - Madam Ada, 1/18/1957 (Box 41)
    - Madame de Treymes, 11/19/1956 (Box 38)
    - Make Believe Mother (The), 11/1/1955 (Box 22)
    - Make-Believe Affair, 5/7/1957 (Box 46)
    - Man and a Maid, 4/8/1956 (Box 30)
    - Man in Half Moon Street (The), 1/9/1957 (Box 40)
    - Man in Seven League Boots, 10/22/1956 (Box 37)
    - Man of the House (The), 4/9/1958 (Box 60)
    - Man Who Wanted to Hate (The), 1/21/1958 (Box 57)
    - Man with the Pointed Toes (The), 1/28/1958 (Box 57)
    - Man without a Country (A), 11/10/1955 (Box 22)
    - Marriage of Convenience, 2/24/1958 (Box 58)
    - Marriage Royal, 9/14/1956 (Box 36)
    - Mask of Venus (The), 3/10/1958 (Box 59)
    - Master Builder (The), 2/14/1957 (Box 42)
    - Mating of Watkins Tottle (The), 3/6/1956 (Box 27)
    - Middle Son (The), 2/13/1956 (Box 26)
    - Middle-Aged Freshman (The), 5/14/1957 (Box 46)
    - Miss Morissa, 1/2/1957 (Box 40)
    - Money in the Bank, 7/2/1957 (Box 48)
    - Monsieur Beaucaire, 2/11/1958 (Box 58)
    - More Than a Man, 1/15/1958 (Box 57)
    - Mr Krane, 3/21/1957 (Box 43)
    - Mr Krane (Commercials), 9/5/1957 (Box 51)
    - Mr Krane (Commercials), 3/21/1957 (Box 44)
    - Mr Pim Passes By, 1/25/1957 (Box 41)
    - Mr Windigo, 6/21/1957 (Box 48)
    - Mrs Moonlight, 3/7/1958 (Box 59)
    - Much Ado About Nothing (Part I), 5/20/1958 (Box 62)
    - Much Ado About Nothing (Part II), 5/21/1958 (Box 62)
    - Mysterious Disappearance, 9/19/1957 (Box 52)
    - Mysterious Mr Todd (The), 2/12/1957 (Box 42)
    - NBC MATINEE THEATRE photographs of illustrations used in presentation of theater in the round (2 items), no date (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Night Cry, 9/18/1957 (Box 52)
    - Night Must Fall, 5/4/1956 (Box 30)
    - Night Train to Chicago, 1/22/1957 (Box 41)
    - Night Train to Chicago (Comm), 6/14/1957 (Box 48)
    - Nightbird Crying (The), 6/6/1958 (Box 63)
    - Nine Finger Jack, 5/19/1958 (Box 62)
    - Nine-Finger Jack, 10/30/1957 (Box 53)
    - Nineteenth Hole (The), 3/19/1957 (Box 43)
    - Nineteenth Hole (The) (Commercials), 7/23/1957 (Box 49)
    - No Time for Comedy, 12/17/1957 (Box 55)
    - Now or Never, 8/23/1957 (Box 51)
    - O Promise Me, 1/31/1956 (Box 25)
    - Old Friend (The), 12/10/1957 (Box 55)
    - Old Maid (The), 1/16/1956 (Box 24)
    - Old Payola (The), 8/8/1956 (Box 34)
    - On Approval, 3/19/1958 (Box 59)
    - On the Trail of the Kingsfeld, 1/14/1957 (Box 40)
    - One for All, 7/25/1957 (Box 49)
    - One for All (Commercials), 3/17/1958 (Box 59)
    - One for the Road, 11/28/1955 (Box 23)
    - One Hundred Red Convertibles, 9/5/1956 (Box 35)
    - One Mummy Too Many, 9/25/1957 (Box 52)
    - One of the Family, 10/25/1956 (Box 37)
    - O'Rourke's House, 3/25/1958 (Box 60)
    - Others (The) (Commercials), 9/30/1957 (Box 52)
    - Others (The) (Commercials), 2/15/1957 (Box 42)
    - Out of My Darkness, 12/3/1957 (Box 54)
    - Out of the Frying Pan (Comm), 10/25/1957 (Box 53)
    - Outing (The), 11/2/1956 (Box 38)
    - Outing (The) (Commercials), 3/13/1957 (Box 43)
    - Papa's Wife, 3/6/1957 (Box 43)
    - Party Dress (The), 6/11/1957 (Box 47)
    - Passing Strange, 12/6/1955 (Box 23)
    - Password (The), 12/19/1956 (Box 39)
    - Peaceable Kingdom (The), 3/18/1957 (Box 43)
    - Pears of Sheba (The), 10/2/1956 (Box 36)
    - People in Glass, 4/11/1956 (Box 28)
    - People vs John Tarr (The), 11/20/1956 (Box 38)
    - Perfect Alibi, 8/10/1956 (Box 35)
    - Persistent Image (The), 11/2/1955 (Box 22)
    - Personal Equation, 9/17/1957 (Box 52)
    - Personnel and studio scheduleings and changes, kine schedules (18 items), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Perspective, 5/9/1956 (Box 30)
    - Phony Venus (The), 4/23/1958 (Box 61)
    - Pigeons and People, 6/19/1957 (Box 48)
    - Pink Hippopotamus (The), 8/30/1956 (Box 35)
    - Plumber in Paradise (A), 11/1/1957 (Box 53)
    - Point of Clearing, 4/10/1957 (Box 45)
    - Portrait in Miniature, 7/15/1957 (Box 49)
    - Price of Scandal (The), 7/5/1957 (Box 49)
    - Pride and Prejudice, 10/1/1956 (Box 36)
    - Prizewinner (The), 3/7/1957 (Box 43)
    - Professional (The), 4/29/1957 (Box 45)
    - Progress and Minnie Sweeney, 11/4/1955 (Box 22)
    - Prominent Citizen, 12/17/1956 (Box 39)
    - Prophet Hosea (The), 3/5/1958 (Box 59)
    - Prosper's Old Mother, 5/1/1958 (Box 61)
    - Pursuit of Happiness, 4/5/1957 (Box 44)
    - Pushover (The), 4/24/1957 (Box 45)
    - Puzzle in the Stars, 5/27/1957 (Box 47)
    - Pygmalion Jones, 8/1/1956 (Box 34)
    - Queen of Spades, 2/28/1957 (Box 43)
    - Question of Balance (A), 9/13/1956 (Box 36)
    - Quiet Street, 4/25/1958 (Box 61)
    - Ransom of Sigmund Freud (The), 11/13/1957 (Box 54)
    - Reach for the Stars, 9/11/1956 (Box 35)
    - Realms of Gold (The), 1/30/1957 (Box 41)
    - Red Sanders Story (The), 12/26/1955 (Box 24)
    - Refugee (The), 12/6/1956 (Box 39)
    - Reluctant Heiress (The), 9/27/1957 (Box 52)
    - Remarkable Mr Jerome (The), 2/19/1957 (Box 42)
    - Remarkable Mr Jerome (The) (Comm), 7/8/1957 (Box 49)
    - Remember Me Kindly, 11/15/1957 (Box 54)
    - Remittance Man (The), 7/26/1956 (Box 33)
    - Return in Winter, 11/7/1957 (Box 53)
    - Reverberator (The), 7/23/1956 (Box 34)
    - Rich Man, Poor Man, 6/10/1957 (Box 47)
    - Richest Man in the World (The), 7/17/1957 (Box 49)
    - Riddle of Mary Murray (The), 5/27/1958 (Box 62)
    - Road to Recovery (The), 6/5/1958 (Box 63)
    - Robin Daw, 3/1/1956 (Box 27)
    - Rocking Chair (The), 3/13/1956 (Box 27)
    - Roman Fever, 11/18/1955 (Box 22)
    - Room and the Groom (The), 12/5/1957 (Box 55)
    - Run for the Money, 10/22/1957 (Box 53)
    - Runaways (The), 2/21/1956 (Box 26)
    - Safe Place (A), 6/18/1956 (Box 32)
    - Santa Is No Saint, 12/22/1955 (Box 24)
    - Sara Crewe, 12/24/1957 (Box 56)
    - Savrola, 11/15/1956 (Box 38)
    - Scandalous Priest (The), 1/3/1957 (Box 40)
    - Seasoned Timber, 7/3/1956 (Box 33)
    - Second-Hand Lover, 5/22/1957 (Box 47)
    - Second-Hand Lover (Commercials), 10/11/1957 (Box 52)
    - See You on Sunday, 12/16/1955 (Box 24)
    - September Tide, no date (Box 63)
    - September Tide, 8/31/1956 (Box 35)
    - Serpent's Tooth (The), 6/12/1956 (Box 32)
    - Shadow and Substance, 3/1/1957 (Box 43)
    - Shake the Stars Down, 10/29/1956 (Box 37)
    - She's the One with the Funny Face, 11/15/1955 (Box 22)
    - Shining Hour (The), 11/9/1956 (Box 38)
    - Shuttered Heart (The), 7/24/1957 (Box 49)
    - Sight Unseen, 10/18/1956 (Box 37)
    - Silent Partner (The), 3/26/1956 (Box 28)
    - Silver Spider (The), 3/28/1958 (Box 60)
    - Sincerely Yours, Charlie Fisher, 1/24/1956 (Box 25)
    - Sing for Me, 10/21/1957 (Box 53)
    - Skylark, 2/27/1956 (Box 26)
    - Smilin' Through, 12/27/1956 (Box 40)
    - Some Blessed People, 4/24/1958 (Box 61)
    - Something About a Dollar, 11/4/1957 (Box 53)
    - Something Stolen, Something Blue, 11/16/1958 (Box 57)
    - Son of Thirty-Seven Fathers, 9/12/1957 (Box 51)
    - Sound of Fear, 9/27/1956 (Box 36)
    - Sound of Fear (The) (Commercials), 6/13/1957 (Box 48)
    - Spare Room (The), 5/21/1956 (Box 31)
    - Spare Your Pity, 11/28/1956 (Box 39)
    - Sport (The), 4/11/1957 (Box 45)
    - Stamp Caddy (The), 10/15/1956 (Box 37)
    - Starmaster (The) (Commercials), 5/17/1957 (Box 46)
    - Statute of Limitations, 5/15/1956 (Box 30)
    - Step Into Darkness, 11/13/1956 (Box 38)
    - Stopover, 6/24/1957 (Box 48)
    - Story of Joseph (The) (Commercials), 4/19/1957 (Box 45)